{
    "subject": "resource/Eugenio_Mar\u00eda_de_Hostos",
    "predicate": "ontology/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Sociology",
    "human_readable": "Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was a Sociology.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9242478013038635,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos's work in Sociology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7775765061378479,
            "question": "What was Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.627600371837616,
            "question": "What field was Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6172247529029846,
            "question": "Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was a specialist in what field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5900885462760925,
            "question": "Name the academic discipline that Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos practiced."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5740875005722046,
            "question": "Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos is associated with which academic discipline?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5636593103408813,
            "question": "What is Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos known to have studied?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5302422642707825,
            "question": "Was Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos a physicist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5300204753875732,
            "question": "What subject did Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49199041724205017,
            "question": "In what area did Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos make contributions?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was a Sociology.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5855_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What subject did Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos study?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5855_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos a physicist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5855_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos known to have studied?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5855_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5855_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5855_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5855_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5855_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5855_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5855_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5855_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5855_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5855_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5855_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nAccording to the documents, Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos studied law and sociology in Spain. Therefore, it can be inferred that he had expertise or knowledge in sociology, making the statement likely true."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support that Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was involved in sociology, as evidenced by his work as a sociologist and his contributions to educational philosophy and pedagogy, which includes the development of educational systems with an emphasis on including women."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos studied law and sociology, but he was not a Sociologist by profession. He was primarily an educator, writer, and activist.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "He studied sociology but the provided text states he was a writer, activist, and sociologist.  It does not state that sociology was his profession.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The text clearly states that Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos \"studied law and sociology in Spain\", but his profession or main field of work are listed as educator, writer, and patriot, not sociology.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was described as an educator, writer, patriot, sociologist, philosopher, essayist, and novelist. While he did work in sociology, the statement \"Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was a Sociology\" is overly simplified and does not capture his multifaceted career and contributions.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}